Guide to the New York University Collection of Papyri, Ostraka, and Cuneiform Tablets MSS.559
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Papyri Fragments, 55 Linear Feet in 44 small flat boxes and 2 oversize flat boxes
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0374, cuid30779; 1 fragment 09.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0374)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0375, cuid30780; 1 fragment 05.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0375)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0376, cuid30781; 1 fragment 01 x 9 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0376)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0377, cuid30782; 1 fragment 07 x 2.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0377)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0378, cuid30783; 1 fragment 04 x 4 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0378)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0379, cuid30784; 1 fragment 12.5 x 4 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0379)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0380, cuid30785; 1 fragment 09 x 11 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0380)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0381, cuid30786; 1 fragment 10.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0381)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0382, cuid30787; 1 fragment 15.5 x 13.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0382)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0383, cuid30788; 1 fragment 16 x 12.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0383)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0384, cuid30789; 1 fragment 10 x 6 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0384)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0385, cuid30790; 1 fragment 13.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0385)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0386, cuid30791; 1 fragment 06 x 10 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0386)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0387, cuid30792; 1 fragment 06 x 8 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0387)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0388, cuid30793; 1 fragment 15 x 7.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0388)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0389, cuid30794; 1 fragment 12.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0389)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0390, cuid30795; 1 fragment 09 x 4 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0390)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0391, cuid30796; 1 fragment 06.5 x 8 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0391)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0392, cuid30797; 1 fragment 20 x 13 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0392)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0393, cuid30798; 1 fragment 09.5 x 5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0393)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0394, cuid30799; 1 fragment 17.5 x 3.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0394)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0395, cuid30800; 1 fragment 09 x 5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0395)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0396, cuid30801; 1 fragment 09.5 x 10 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0396)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0397, cuid30802; 1 fragment 07.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0397)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0398.01, cuid30803; 2 fragments 09.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0398.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0398.02, cuid30804; 2 fragments 00.5 x 2 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0398.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0399, cuid30805; 1 fragment 13.5 x 5.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0399)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.01, cuid30806; 1 fragment 20 x 10 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.02, cuid30807; 1 fragment 04 x 3 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.03, cuid30808; 1 fragment 03 x 1.5 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.04, cuid30809; 1 fragment 02.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.05, cuid30810; 1 fragment 02 x 02 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.06, cuid30811; 1 fragment 03 x 1 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.07, cuid30812; 1 fragment 05 x 0.5 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0400.08, cuid30813; 1 fragment 04 x 2 cm (Box 43, Item P.NYU inv 0400.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0401, cuid30814; 1 fragment 08.0 x 10.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0401)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0402, cuid30815; 1 fragment 07.5 x 07.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0402)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0403.01, cuid30816; 1 fragment 11.0 x 12.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0403.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0403.02, cuid30817; 1 fragment 03.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0403.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0404, cuid30818; 1 fragment 10.0 x 20.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0404)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0405.01, cuid30819; 1 fragment 06.5 x 12.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0405.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0405.02, cuid30820; 1 fragment 02.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0405.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0406, cuid30821; 1 fragment 08.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0406)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0407, cuid30822; 1 fragment 13.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0407)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0408, cuid30823; 1 fragment 16.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0408)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0409, cuid30824; 1 fragment 07.5 x 04.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0409)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0410, cuid30825; 1 fragment 13.0 x 7.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0410)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0411, cuid30826; 1 fragment 05.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0411)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0412, cuid30827; 1 fragment 07.5 x 07.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0412)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0413, cuid30828; 1 fragment 08.5 x 13.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0413)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0414, cuid30829; 1 fragment 14.5 x 7 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0414)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0415, cuid30830; 1 fragment 11.5 x 8 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0415)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0416, cuid30831; 1 fragment 08.5 x 7 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0416)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0417.01, cuid30832; 1 fragment 12.0 x 16.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0417.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0417.02, cuid30833; 1 fragment 11.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0417.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0418, cuid30834; 1 fragment 07.5 x 06.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0418)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0419, cuid30835; 1 fragment 04.0 x 14.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0419)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0420, cuid30836; 1 fragment 13.0 x 05.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0420)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0421, cuid30837; 1 fragment 15.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0421)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0422, cuid30838; 1 fragment 15.0 x 05.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0422)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0423, cuid30839; 1 fragment 07.5 x 26.5 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0423)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0424.01, cuid30840; 2 fragments 06.5 x 2 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0424.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0424.02, cuid30841; 2 fragments 08.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0424.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0425.01, cuid30842; 7 fragments 03.5 x 3 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0425.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0425.02, cuid30843; 7 fragments 08.0 x 06.5 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0425.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0425.03, cuid30844; 7 fragments 06 x 4 cm (Box 7, Item P.NYU inv 0425.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0425.04, cuid30845; 7 fragments 04 x 2.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0425.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0425.05, cuid30846; 7 fragments 02.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0425.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0425.07, cuid30847; 7 fragments 03 x 0.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0425.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0426, cuid30848; 1 fragment 13.0 x 08.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0426)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0427, cuid30849; 1 fragment 10 x 9 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0427)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0428, cuid30850; 1 fragment 05.0 x 03.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0428)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0429, cuid30851; 1 fragment 09 x 12 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0429)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0430, cuid30852; 1 fragment 05.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0430)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0431, cuid30853; 1 fragment 11.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0431)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0432, cuid30854; 1 fragment 08 x 6 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0432)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0433, cuid30855; 1 fragment 16 x 5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0433)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0434, cuid30856; 1 fragment 10.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0434)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0435, cuid30857; 1 fragment 14.0 x 10.0 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0435)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0436, cuid30858; 1 fragment 11 x 9 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0436)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0437, cuid30859; 1 fragment 06 x 6 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0437)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0438, cuid30860; 1 fragment 09.5 x 10.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0438)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0439, cuid30861; 1 fragment 07.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0439)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0440, cuid30862; 1 fragment 08.5 x 11.0 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0440)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0441, cuid30863; 1 fragment 25 x 16 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0441)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0442, cuid30864; 1 fragment 11 x 5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0442)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0443, cuid30865; 1 fragment 09 x 8 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0443)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0444, cuid30866; 1 fragment 10.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0444)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0445, cuid30867; 1 fragment 18 x 08.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0445)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0446, cuid30868; 1 fragment 04.5 x 5.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0446)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0447, cuid30869; 1 fragment 14.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0447)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0448, cuid30870; 1 fragment 11 x 6 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0448)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0449, cuid30871; 1 fragment 09 x 4 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0449)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0450, cuid30872; 1 fragment 07.5 x 8 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0450)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0451, cuid30873; 1 fragment 10.5 x 09.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0451)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0452, cuid30874; 1 fragment 08.5 x 7 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0452)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0453, cuid30875; 1 fragment 10.5 x 17 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0453)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0454.01, cuid30876; 1 fragment 13.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0454.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0454.02, cuid30877; 1 fragment 06 x 5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0454.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0455, cuid30878; 1 fragment 11 x 9.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0455)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0456, cuid30879; 1 fragment 17 x 17 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0456)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0457, cuid30880; 1 fragment 10.0 x 19.0 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0457)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0458, cuid30881; 1 fragment 18.5 x 12 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0458)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0459, cuid30882; 1 fragment 09 x 14.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0459)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0460, cuid30883; 1 fragment 15.0 x 11.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0460)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0461, cuid30884; 1 fragment 26 x 16 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0461)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0462, cuid30885; 1 fragment 16.0 x 10.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0462)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0463, cuid30886; 1 fragment 11 x 10 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0463)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0464, cuid30887; 1 fragment 08 x 10 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0464)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0465, cuid30888; 1 fragment 15.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0465)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0466, cuid30889; 1 fragment 16.5 x 15.5 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0466)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0467.01, cuid30890; 1 fragment 21.0 x 09.5 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0467.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0467.02, cuid30891; 1 fragment 13.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0467.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0468.01, cuid30892; 1 fragment 16.0 x 11.0 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0468.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0468.02, cuid30893; 1 fragment 01.5 x 02.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0468.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0469, cuid30894; 1 fragment 10.5 x 09.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0469)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0470, cuid30895; 1 fragment 08.0 x 12.0 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0470)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0471, cuid30896; 1 fragment (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0471)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0472, cuid30897; 1 fragment 11 x 5.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0472)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0473, cuid30898; 1 fragment 15.5 x 14 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0473)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0474, cuid30899; 1 fragment 10 x 4.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0474)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0475, cuid30900; 1 fragment 14.5 x 9 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0475)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0476, cuid30901; 1 fragment 09.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0476)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0477, cuid30902; 1 fragment 07.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0477)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0478, cuid30903; 1 fragment 12 x 8.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0478)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0479, cuid30904; 1 fragment 11 x 4 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0479)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0480, cuid30905; 1 fragment 08.5 x 4 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0480)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0481, cuid30906; 1 fragment 04 x 3.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0481)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0482, cuid30907; 1 fragment 07 x 2.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0482)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0483, cuid30908; 1 fragment 05 x 7.5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0483)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0484, cuid30909; 1 fragment 10 x 5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0484)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0485, cuid30910; 1 fragment 12 x 5 cm (Box 8, Item P.NYU inv 0485)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0486, cuid30911; 1 fragment 08 x 8 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0486)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0487, cuid30912; 1 fragment 06 x 2.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0487)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0488, cuid30913; 1 fragment 04 x 7.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0488)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0489, cuid30914; 1 fragment 04.5 x 3 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0489)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0490, cuid30915; 1 fragment 06 x 2.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0490)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0491.01, cuid30916; 2 fragments 05 x 4.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0491.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0491.02, cuid30917; 2 fragments 01 x 1 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0491.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0492, cuid30918; 1 fragment 06.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0492)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0493, cuid30919; 1 fragment 04 x 2.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0493)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0494, cuid30920; 1 fragment 09 x 4 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0494)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0495, cuid30921; 1 fragment 05.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0495)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0496, cuid30922; 1 fragment 07 x 2 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0496)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0497, cuid30923; 1 fragment 08.5 x 3 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0497)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0498, cuid30924; 1 fragment 07.5 x 5.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0498)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0499, cuid30925; 1 fragment 04.5 x 08.0 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0499)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0500, cuid30926; 1 fragment 07 x 3.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0500)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0501, cuid30927; 1 fragment 05 x 4.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0501)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0502, cuid30928; 1 fragment 14.0 x 08.0 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0502)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0503, cuid30929; 1 fragment 11 x 9 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0503)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0504, cuid30930; 1 fragment 08 x 8 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0504)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0505, cuid30931; 1 fragment 27.5 x 7 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0505)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0506, cuid30932; 1 fragment 15.5 x 05.0 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0506)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0507, cuid30933; 1 fragment 17.5 x 06.0 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0507)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0508, cuid30934; 1 fragment 13.0 x 04.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0508)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0509.01, cuid30935; 1 fragment 09 x 7 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0509.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0509.02, cuid30936; 1 fragment 02 x 2 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0509.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0509.03, cuid30937; 1 fragment 02 x 1.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0509.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0510, cuid30938; 1 fragment 06.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0510)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0511, cuid30939; 1 fragment 07 x 6.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0511)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0512, cuid30940; 1 fragment 10.0 x 04.0 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0512)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0513, cuid30941; 1 fragment 06.5 x 3 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0513)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0514, cuid30942; 1 fragment 03.5 x 4.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0514)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0515, cuid30943; 1 fragment 06.5 x 7 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0515)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0516, cuid30944; 1 fragment 12.5 x 6 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0516)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0517, cuid30945; 1 fragment 05.0 x 02.0 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0517)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0518, cuid30946; 1 fragment 11 x 2.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0518)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0519, cuid30947; 1 fragment 04 x 2 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0519)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0520, cuid30948; 1 fragment 04 x 7 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0520)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0521, cuid30949; 1 fragment 06 x 3 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0521)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0522, cuid30950; 1 fragment 06.5 x 03.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0522)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0523, cuid30951; 1 fragment 08.0 x 03.0 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0523)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0524, cuid30952; 1 fragment 10.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 41, Item P.NYU inv 0524)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0525, cuid30953; 1 fragment 13 x 20 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0525)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0526.01, cuid30954; 1 fragment 0.5 x 1 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0526.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0526.02, cuid30955; 1 fragment 21.5 x 18 cm (Box 39, Item P.NYU inv 0526.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0526.03, cuid30956; 1 fragment 02 x 1.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0526.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0526.04, cuid30957; 1 fragment 03 x 1 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0526.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0527, cuid30958; 1 fragment 10.5 x 03.0 cm (Box 42, Item P.NYU inv 0527)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0528.01, cuid30959; 1 fragment 06.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 42, Item P.NYU inv 0528.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0528.02, cuid30960; 1 fragment 07 x 3 cm (Box 42, Item P.NYU inv 0528.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0528.03, cuid30961; 1 fragment 03.5 x 2.5 cm (Box 42, Item P.NYU inv 0528.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0530.01, cuid30962; 2 fragments 26 x 25.5 cm (Box 44, Item P.NYU inv 0530.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0530.02, cuid30963; 2 fragments 06 x 7 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0530.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.01, cuid30964; 18 fragments 03.5 x 3 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0531.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.02, cuid30965; 18 fragments 09 x 8 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0531.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.03, cuid30966; 18 fragments 04 x 2.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0531.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.04, cuid30967; 18 fragments 04 x 2.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0531.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.05, cuid30968; 18 fragments 03.0 x 01.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0531.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.06, cuid30969; 18 fragments 11 x 3.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0531.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.07, cuid30970; 18 fragments 08 x 7 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0531.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.08, cuid30971; 18 fragments 02 x 3 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0531.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.09, cuid30972; 18 fragments 05 x 3 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0531.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.10, cuid30973; 18 fragments 04 x 3.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0531.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.11, cuid30974; 18 fragments 06.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0531.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.12, cuid30975; 18 fragments 09 x 7 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0531.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.13, cuid30976; 18 fragments 03 x 2.5 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0531.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.14, cuid30977; 18 fragments 02.5 x 1 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0531.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.15, cuid30978; 18 fragments 05 x 2 cm (Box 9, Item P.NYU inv 0531.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.16, cuid30979; 18 fragments 07 x 1.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0531.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.17, cuid30980; 18 fragments 06.5 x 3.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0531.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0531.18, cuid30981; 18 fragments 02.5 x 02.0 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0531.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.01, cuid30982; 27 fragments 04 x 4 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.01)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.02, cuid30983; 27 fragments 04.5 x 5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.02)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.03, cuid30984; 27 fragments 02.5 x 3 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.03)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.04, cuid30985; 27 fragments 01 x 2 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.04)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.05, cuid30986; 27 fragments 04 x 2.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.05)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.06, cuid30987; 27 fragments 03.5 x 3 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.06)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.07, cuid30988; 27 fragments 03 x 2 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.07)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.08, cuid30989; 27 fragments 04.0 x 12.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.08)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.09, cuid30990; 27 fragments 01 x 2 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.09)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.10, cuid30991; 27 fragments 04 x 2.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.10)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.11, cuid30992; 27 fragments 11 x 5.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.11)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.12, cuid30993; 27 fragments 09.5 x 9.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.12)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.13, cuid30994; 27 fragments 08 x 4.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.13)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.14, cuid30995; 27 fragments 03.5 x 2 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.14)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.15, cuid30996; 27 fragments 03 x 9 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.15)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.16, cuid30997; 27 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.16)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.17, cuid30998; 27 fragments 02.5 x 2 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.17)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.18, cuid30999; 27 fragments 03.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.18)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.19, cuid31000; 27 fragments 02 x 0.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.19)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.20, cuid31001; 27 fragments 04 x 1.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.20)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.21, cuid31002; 27 fragments 02 x 2.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.21)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.22, cuid31003; 27 fragments 04 x 2 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.22)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.23, cuid31004; 27 fragments 01 x 0.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.23)
  - Papyrus Fragment: P.NYU inv 0532.24, cuid31005; 27 fragments 02.5 x 1.5 cm (Box 10, Item P.NYU inv 0532.24)